gameplay.co.uk 2015-06-23

# Privacy Policy | GAME

At GAME we are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). Our data protection registration is Z3151729.

We collect information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.

We will not email you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us.

The type of information we collect about you includes:

• Your name  
• Your address  
• Your email address  
• Your phone number  
• Your credit / debit card details  
• Your order history and profile

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by contacting our Customer Services department.

If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct them.

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

To ensure that your credit, debit or charge card is not being used without your consent, we will validate name, address and other personal information supplied by you during the order process against appropriate third party databases. By accepting these terms and conditions you consent to such checks being made. In performing these checks personal information provided by you may be disclosed to a registered Identity Reference Agency which may keep a record of the information. You can rest assured that this is done only to confirm your identity and that there is active credit at the name and address supplied. Please note that although an actual credit check is not performed the search may be logged on your file but your credit rating will be unaffected. All information provided by you will be treated securely and strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

We use CyberSource for processing of security information and this data is passed outside the EEA (European Economic Area) to the U.S.A. and then back to the UK. CyberSource has been certified by Visa, U.S.A. and Visa International as being compliant with the Cardholder Information Security Program and the Account Information Security program, respectively, which must be renewed annually after follow-up audits. To date, these are the most stringent security requirements in the industry having to do with how consumer data is secured, technologically as well as from a process standpoint.

We will share your details with companies directly involved in getting you the product you have ordered. In these cases GAME will ensure that there is no further use of your data other than to deliver you the product and arrange for that delivery, and to support guarantees or maintenance in the future. In the majority of cases they will have no right to market to you directly unless you specifically request it, and will be registered under UK data protection law, where they do have the right to market to you direct you will be specifically asked to opt-in.

We use Responsys to send out e-mails to those who have chosen to receive e-mailings from us. Responsys does not use any of the information from our mailing lists except to send and process e-mail communications on our behalf. Read the [Responsys statement on privacy and permissions marketing](http://policy1.responsys.net/permission.htm).

We use Coremetrics for web analytics. Coremetrics, Inc. ("Coremetrics") collects and processes personal information from the European Union in four discrete ways: (1) Via Coremetrics' web site. The personal information collected from users online or otherwise constitutes general account or enquiry information including contact information such as company name, first and last name, title, username and password, phone and email address; (2) From Coremetrics' European-based operations, employees, agents and consultants in respect of their sales activity and leads, customer relationship management, general business activities and compliance activities; (3) Via Coremetrics' business optimization service provided to GAME via an online product named Coremetrics Analytics. However, via JavaScript code and transparent gifs tagged on our web pages, Coremetrics may collect and track data about how these web pages are visited. In certain instances the tagged web pages may provide Coremetrics with personal information such as information about a visitor's IP address. In addition, the tagged web pages may provide Coremetrics with personal information such as a cookie profile and email which (when combined with other information held by Coremetrics or GAME) may lead to the identification of an individual and the uses they make of the website and services; and (4) Via Coremetrics' automated bid management and analytics service provided to GAME via an online product named Coremetrics Intelligent Offer. In some instances, on behalf of GAME, Coremetrics intelligent Offer enables GAME to pin-point search engine keywords most relevant to geographic, behavioral and other desired profiling information. In such circumstances, all such information is owned and controlled by GAME and Coremetrics has no relationship (or transparency) to such web site visitors. Coremetrics trusts (as well as requires via its terms and conditions of service) GAME to make adequate disclosures to Coremetrics as a third party processor. Coremetrics acts as a data processor on behalf of GAME in relation to such personal information. Read the [Coremetrics statement on privacy](http://www.ibm.com/privacy/us/en/).

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. Should you wish to browse anonymously please contact us and request a link that we can send you to exclude you from web tracking.

If you have any questions/ comments about privacy, you should contact our Customer Services. If you contact us for details of existing information that we hold about you it is important that you quote your original email address, as used at the time you first contacted us. We may be unable to trace your details without this.
